If there’s one rule that most parents cling to in the confusing, fast-changing world of kids and media, it’s “No screens before age 2.”
在儿童与媒体这个令人困惑、瞬息万变的领域里，如果说有哪条规则是大多数家长都坚守不放的，那就是“2岁前不接触屏幕”。
As of today, that rule has been thrown out the window.
从今天起，这条规则被彻底抛弃了。
The American Academy of Pediatrics (AAP), which first issued that recommendation back in 1999, has extensively updated and revised its guidelines for children and adolescents to reflect new research and new habits.
美国儿科学会（AAP）早在1999年就首次提出了这一建议，如今已全面更新、修订了针对儿童和青少年的指南，以反映新的研究和新的习惯。
The new guidelines, especially for very young children, shift the focus from WHAT is on the screen to WHO else is in the room.
新指南把关注的重点从屏幕上是“什么”转到了房间里还有“谁”，针对幼童的部分尤其如此。
And in doing so, they raise some intriguing points about the future of learning from media.
而这样一来，对于通过媒体学习的未来，新指南也提出了一些耐人寻味的观点。
For babies younger than 18 months, the AAP still says no screens at all is the best idea—with one notable exception: live video chat.
对于不满18个月的婴儿，美国儿科学会仍然表示，完全不接触屏幕是最好的做法，但有一个值得注意的例外：实时视频聊天。
Surveys indicate that families already popularly believe that “FaceTime doesn’t count”, or at least that the benefit of virtual visits with grandparents or other relatives outweighs the potential cost of exposing babies to the laptop or smartphone.
调查显示，各家庭已普遍认为“FaceTime不算数”，或者至少认为，和祖父母或其他亲戚线上见面的好处，超过了让婴儿接触笔记本电脑或智能手机的潜在代价。
The AAP doesn’t cite positive evidence that infants actually get something out of this kind of “conversation”, the way that they clearly do from live social interaction.
婴儿显然能从面对面的社交互动中获益，但美国儿科学会并没有援引确凿的证据，证明他们从这类“对话”中也真能有所收获。
But there’s some observational research showing that infants as young as six months old are emotionally engaged by playing live peekaboo with Grandma online.
不过，有一些观察性研究表明，年仅6个月大的婴儿通过网络和奶奶实时玩躲猫猫游戏时，会在情感上投入其中。
For infants and toddlers, ages 15 months to 2 years old, there’s limited evidence from a couple of very small studies that they can learn new words from educational media, if and only if parents are watching alongside them, repeating what the video says and/or drawing attention to what is on the screen.
对于15个月至2岁的婴儿和学步儿童，有两三项规模很小的研究提供了有限的证据，表明当且仅当父母在一旁陪着一起看，复述视频里说的话和/或提醒孩子注意屏幕上的内容时，这些孩子才能从教育类媒体中学到新词。
In other words, treating a video or an app like a picture book is the best bet.
换句话说，像对待图画书那样对待视频或应用程序，是最稳妥的做法。
The flip side of this is that many studies have actually shown poorer language skills correlated with earlier solo viewing of “educational” videos.
而事情的另一面是，许多研究实际上已经表明，较差的语言能力与较早独自观看“教育类”视频相关。
There’s also research that shows language delays in children who watch more TV and start watching earlier.
还有研究表明，电视看得更多、更早开始看电视的孩子存在语言发育迟缓的情况。
In both cases, the problem seems to be media replacing interaction with people.
在这两种情况下，问题似乎都在于媒体取代了与人的互动。
For this reason, the new AAP guideline has changed from “avoid all screens under age 2” to “avoid solo media use in this age group.”
正因如此，美国儿科学会的新指南已经从“2岁以下避免接触一切屏幕”改为“这一年龄段避免独自使用媒体”。
For preschoolers ages 2 to 5, there’s more evidence that they have the ability to transfer knowledge from screens to the real world, including early literacy and math.
对于2至5岁的学龄前儿童，有更多证据表明，他们有能力把知识从屏幕迁移到现实世界中，包括早期读写和数学方面的知识。
For this age group, the AAP recommends no more than an hour a day of screen use.
对于这一年龄段的孩子，美国儿科学会建议每天使用屏幕不超过一小时。
And, just as with younger children, it wants care-givers to take part in screen time: “Co-view with your children, help children understand what they are seeing, and help them apply what they learn to the world around them.”
而且，和对年龄更小的孩子一样，该学会希望看护人在孩子看屏幕时参与其中：“和孩子一起看，帮助孩子理解所看到的内容，并帮助他们把学到的东西运用到周围的世界中。”